tidyrepo.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Tidy Repo

At www.tidyrepo.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extremely important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and may be collected by www.tidyrepo.com and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other web sites, www.tidyrepo.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes IP addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider info, date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies & Data**

We use “cookies”. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s computer to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies may also enable us to track and target user interests to improve the experience on our website in the future.

  * we don’t collect personal information unless it is needed (ex: newsletter and pools)
  * we don’t share your personal information except to comply with the law
  * we don’t store your personal information on our servers unless it’s required to operate one of our website services (ex: comments)

Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information about you. Any personal information is only collected when you voluntarily provide it, such as providing your email address to subscribe to a newsletter. The following is a list of possible cookies and data collected when using Tidy Repo. Please refer to each service’s privacy policy for more information on the exact types of data collected:

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Protection of Information**  
Tidy Repo takes all reasonable measures necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

 **Privacy Policy Changes**  
Tidy Repo reserves the right to change this policy at any time. We encourage visitors to check this page for Privacy Policy updates regularly. Continued use of this website after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at info[at]tidyrepo(dot)com.
